<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Eso po</title>
    <link>http://dtorres.me/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Eso po</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Diego Torres (and Aatr tits)</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2017 23:22:05 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://dtorres.me/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Amatka</title>
      <link>http://dtorres.me/blog/post/amatka/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2017 23:22:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dtorres.me/blog/post/amatka/</guid>
      <description>I started reading Jagannath (a compilation of stories by Karin Tidbeck, the author) and before I realized, I was embraced by her narration style, submerged yet not drowning.
It was easy to imagine scenery, the characters and feel moved by them.
So after a couple stories I started reading Amatka1, with no knowledge whatsoever about it, no summary, no context or prior recommendation but a quote by Ann Leckie2 praising it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Distance</title>
      <link>http://dtorres.me/blog/post/distance-verses/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2017 21:54:57 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dtorres.me/blog/post/distance-verses/</guid>
      <description>For days we&amp;rsquo;ve talked.
Long hours at times
Of your problems, and mine.
Sometimes neglecting your sleep
Sometimes neglecting mine.
You&amp;rsquo;re hurting, I know
I yearn to hug you
distance makes it hard
Hours have passed.
My crave for hugging,
has not.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts on Affinity Photo</title>
      <link>http://dtorres.me/blog/post/thoughts-on-afphoto/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2017 19:01:09 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dtorres.me/blog/post/thoughts-on-afphoto/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been using Photoshop to process and develop the RAW pictures I take with my Canon 80D, and it does a great job at it, but it is an overkill of a tool to have considering most of my time is spent in the RAW Camera screen.
I&amp;rsquo;ve been aware of Affinity Photo for a while now but I hadn&amp;rsquo;t felt compelled to try it until the iPad version came out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crushes</title>
      <link>http://dtorres.me/blog/post/crushes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2017 13:13:17 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dtorres.me/blog/post/crushes/</guid>
      <description>I like having a crush, the expectation, planning, hope and possibilities that come from this seemingly unexpected feeling.
I dread however, having to put myself in the other person perspective as this is a mostly one sided and proofless experience, only having met them a short while ago, I have barely any context or information on how they would react if they were to find out I like them.
This in turn makes me anxious and hyperaware of my actions when we are together, hindering what, it seems, people like most about me, my improvised jokes and attention to detail on random things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tipping Point</title>
      <link>http://dtorres.me/blog/post/tipping-point/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2017 12:23:43 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dtorres.me/blog/post/tipping-point/</guid>
      <description>It felt great, just like the first time they cuddled, bodies close, his arms around her and peace. The same peace that kept her from leaving that first night.
He lift his head and whispered into her ear:
– How would you feel about having kids?
Oh no, it&amp;rsquo;s been two years, two wonderful if intense years together, he is wonderful, and stupid me hadn&amp;rsquo;t told him. Oh no.
– I am infertile – she said, as tears started running down her cheeks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Proposal] Rename fatalError() API</title>
      <link>http://dtorres.me/blog/post/proposal-fatalerror/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2017 22:53:25 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dtorres.me/blog/post/proposal-fatalerror/</guid>
      <description>Note: The following text was first posted in the Swift evolution mailing list
Introduction This function was introduced along others to halt execution of the running instance to convey a state of affairs without resolution whatsoever. This proposal lays the case that this function is not performing its stated mission and attempts to help it come forward with its real intentions in order to have a better conformance with the Swift naming guidelines.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Collatz conjecture and IndexSets</title>
      <link>http://dtorres.me/blog/post/collatz-indexset/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2016 00:20:05 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dtorres.me/blog/post/collatz-indexset/</guid>
      <description>I was watching Numberphile videos when I stumbled upon the Collatz conjecture. It’s a mind boggling complex positive integer sequence derived from a function with 2 rules:
 If n is even, divide by 2
 If n is odd, triple it and add one
  This process is repeated until 1 is reached, which, as seen from the previous rules, recurses into [1, 4, 2, 1…]. But, do all numbers reach 1 eventually?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The GIF is dead</title>
      <link>http://dtorres.me/blog/post/gif-is-dead/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dtorres.me/blog/post/gif-is-dead/</guid>
      <description>Nowadays when we use the word GIF, hardly it refers to the file format, rather we talk about a really short motion picture (often loopable) without sound.
We hardly think of the actual file format used to display these (unless it takes too long to load, then it surely is a G.I.F.)
As such I think we can at last please Steve Wilhite and give him the pronunciation he always wanted by introducing this separation of concepts apt for today:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Storing related data in NSURLRequest</title>
      <link>http://dtorres.me/blog/post/storing-info-nsurlrequest/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dtorres.me/blog/post/storing-info-nsurlrequest/</guid>
      <description>Basically what we are going to do is use and profit from NSURLRequest&amp;rsquo;s being conformant to NSCoding, and a little known API from NSURLProtocol which allows us attach info to requests.
//Step 0: For the purpose of this gist, we&#39;ll already have a //background session setup and assume a bunch of stuff. NSURLSession *bgSession = [NSURLSession magicMethodWhichGivesMeTheAlreadySetupSession]; //Geeez, Methods are long in Obj-C.  //IMPORTANT: Request must be mutable in order for this to work.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>